Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65
- Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.3 (1964: Jan. 17)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.4 (1964: Jan. 24)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.5 (1964: Jan. 31)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.6 (1964: Feb. 7)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.7 (1964: Feb. 14)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.8 (1964: Feb. 21)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.9 (1964: Feb. 28)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.10 (1964: Mar. 6)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.11 (1964: Mar. 13)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.12 (1964: Mar. 20)
  - Item 13: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.13 (1964: Mar. 27)
  - Item 14: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.14 (1964: Apr. 3)
  - Item 15: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.15 (1964: Apr. 10)
  - Item 16: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.16 (1964: Apr. 17)
  - Item 17: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.17 (1964: Apr. 24)
  - Item 18: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.18 (1964: May 1)
  - Item 19: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.19 (1964: May 8)
  - Item 20: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.20 (1964: May 15)
  - Item 21: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.21 (1964: May 22)
  - Item 22: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.22 (1964: May 29)
  - Item 23: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.23 (1964: June 5)
  - Item 24: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.24 (1964: June 12)
  - Item 25: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.25 (1964: June 19)
  - Item 26: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.26 (1964: June 26)
  - Item 27: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.27 (1964: July 3)
  - Item 28: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.28 (1964: july 10)
  - Item 29: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.29 (1964: July 17)
  - Item 30: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.30 (1964: July 24)
  - Item 31: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.31 (1964: July 31)
  - Item 32: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.32 (1964: Aug. 7)
  - Item 33: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.33 (1964: Aug. 14)
  - Item 34: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.34 (1964: Aug. 21)
  - Item 35: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.35 (1964: Aug. 28)
  - Item 36: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.36 (1964: Sept. 4)
  - Item 37: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.37 (1964: Sept. 11)
  - Item 38: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.38 (1964: Sept. 18)
  - Item 39: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.39 (1964: Sept. 25)
  - Item 40: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.40 (1964: Oct. 2)
  - Item 41: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.41 (1964: Oct. 9)
  - Item 42: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.42 (1964: Oct. 16)
  - Item 43: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.43 (1964: Oct. 23)
  - Item 44: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.44 (1964: Oct. 30)
  - Item 45: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.45 (1964: Nov. 6)
  - Item 46: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.46 (1964: Nov. 13)
  - Item 47: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.47 (1964: Nov. 20)
  - Item 48: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.48 (1964: Nov. 27)
  - Item 49: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.49 (1964: Dec. 4)
  - Item 50: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.50 (1964: Dec. 11)
  - Item 51: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.51 (1964: Dec. 18)
  - Item 52: Locomotive Engineer, 1964; Publication (Box 47, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.98:no.52 (1964: Dec. 25)
- Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.1 (1965: Jan. 1)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.2 (1965: Jan. 8)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.3 (1965: Jan. 15)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.4 (1965: Jan. 22)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.5 (1965: Jan. 29)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.6 (1965: Feb. 5)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.7 (1965: Feb. 12)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.8 (1965: Feb. 19)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.9 (1965: Feb. 16)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.10 (1965: Mar. 5)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.11 (1965: Mar. 12)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.12 (1965: Mar. 19)
  - Item 13: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.13 (1965: Mar. 26)
  - Item 14: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.14 (1965: Apr. 2)
  - Item 15: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.15 (1965: Apr. 9)
  - Item 16: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.16 (1965: Apr. 16)
  - Item 17: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.17 (1965: Apr. 23)
  - Item 18: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.18 (1965: Apr. 30)
  - Item 19: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.19 (1965: May 7)
  - Item 20: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.20 (1965: May 14)
  - Item 21: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.21 (1965: May 21)
  - Item 22: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.22 (1965: May 28)
  - Item 23: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.23 (1965: June 4)
  - Item 24: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.24 (1965: June 11)
  - Item 25: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.25 (1965: June 18)
  - Item 26: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.26 (1965: June 25)
  - Item 27: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.27 (1965: July 2)
  - Item 28: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.28 (1965: July 9)
  - Item 29: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.29 (1965: July 16)
  - Item 30: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.30 (1965: July 23)
  - Item 31: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.31 (1965: July 30)
  - Item 32: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.32 (1965: Aug. 6)
  - Item 33: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.33 (1965: Aug. 13)
  - Item 34: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.34 (1965: Aug. 20)
  - Item 35: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.35 (1965: Aug. 27)
  - Item 36: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.36 (1965: Sept. 3)
  - Item 37: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.37 (1965: Sept. 10)
  - Item 38: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.38 (1965: Sept. 17)
  - Item 39: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.39 (1965: Sept. 24)
  - Item 40: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.40 (1965: Oct. 1)
  - Item 41: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.41 (1965: Oct. 8)
  - Item 42: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.42 (1965: Oct. 15)
  - Item 43: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.43 (1965: Oct. 22)
  - Item 44: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.44 (1965: Oct. 29)
  - Item 45: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.45 (1965: Nov. 5)
  - Item 46: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.46 (1965: Nov. 12)
  - Item 47: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.47 (1965: Nov. 19)
  - Item 48: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.48 (1965: Nov. 26)
  - Item 49: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.49 (1965: Dec. 3)
  - Item 50: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.50 (1965: Dec. 10)
  - Item 51: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.51 (1965: Dec. 17)
  - Item 52: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.52 (1965: Dec. 24)
  - Item 53: Locomotive Engineer, 1965; Publication (Box 47, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.99:no.53 (1965: Dec. 31)
- Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.1 (1966: Jan. 7)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.2 (1966: Jan. 14)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.3 (1966: Jan. 21)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.4 (1966: Jan. 28)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.5 (1966: Feb. 4)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.6 (1966: Feb. 11)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.7 (1966: Feb. 18)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.8 (1966: Feb. 25)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.9 (1966: Mar. 4)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.10 (1966: Mar. 11)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.11 (1966: Mar. 18)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.12 (1966: Mar. 25)
  - Item 13: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.13 (1966: Apr. 1)
  - Item 14: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.14 (1966: Apr. 8)
  - Item 15: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.15 (1966: Apr. 15)
  - Item 16: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.16 (1966: Apr. 22)
  - Item 17: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.17 (1966: Apr. 29)
  - Item 18: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.18 (1966: May 6)
  - Item 19: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.19 (1966: May 13)
  - Item 20: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.20 (1966: May 20)
  - Item 21: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.21 (1966: May 27)
  - Item 22: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.22 (1966: June 3)
  - Item 23: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.23 (1966: June 10)
  - Item 24: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.24 (1966: June 17)
  - Item 25: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.25 (1966: June 24)
  - Item 26: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.26 (1966: July 1)
  - Item 27: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.27 (1966: July 8)
  - Item 28: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.28 (1966: July 15)
  - Item 29: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.29 (1966: July 22)
  - Item 30: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.30 (1966: July 29)
  - Item 31: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.31 (1966: Aug. 5)
  - Item 32: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.32 (1966: Aug. 12)
  - Item 33: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.33 (1966: Aug. 19)
  - Item 34: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.34 (1966: Aug. 26)
  - Item 35: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.35 (1966: Sept. 2)
  - Item 36: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.36 (1966: Sept. 9)
  - Item 37: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.37 (1966: Sept. 16)
  - Item 38: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.38 (1966: Sept. 23)
  - Item 39: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.39 (1966: Sept. 30)
  - Item 40: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.40 (1966: Oct. 7)
  - Item 41: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.41 (1966: Oct. 14)
  - Item 42: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.42 (1966: Oct. 21)
  - Item 43: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.43 (1966: Oct. 28)
  - Item 44: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.44 (1966: Nov. 4)
  - Item 45: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.45 (1966: Nov. 11)
  - Item 46: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.46 (1966: Nov. 18)
  - Item 47: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.47 (1966: Dec. 2)
  - Item 48: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.48 (1966: Dec. 9)
  - Item 49: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.49 (1966: Dec. 16)
  - Item 50: Locomotive Engineer, 1966; Publication (Box 47, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.100:no.50 (1966: Dec. 23)
- Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.1 (1967: Jan. 6)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.2 (1967: Jan. 13)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.3 (1967: Jan. 20)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.4 (1967: Jan. 27)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.5 (1967: Feb. 3)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.6 (1967: Feb. 10)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.7 (1967: Feb. 17)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.8 (1967: Feb. 24)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.9 (1967: Mar. 3)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.10 (1967: Mar. 10)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.11 (1967: Mar. 17)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.12 (1967: Mar. 24)
  - Item 13: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.13 (1967: Mar. 31)
  - Item 14: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.14 (1967: Apr. 7)
  - Item 15: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.15 (1967: Apr. 14)
  - Item 16: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.16 (1967: Apr. 21)
  - Item 17: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.17 (1967: Apr. 28)
  - Item 18: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.18 (1967: May 5)
  - Item 19: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.19 (1967: May 12)
  - Item 20: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.20 (1967: May 19)
  - Item 21: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.21 (1967: May 26)
  - Item 22: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.22 (1967: June 9)
  - Item 23: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.23 (1967: June 16)
  - Item 24: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.24 (1967: June 23)
  - Item 25: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.25 (1967: June 30)
  - Item 26: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.26 (1967: July 14)
  - Item 27: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.27 (1967: July 21)
  - Item 28: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.28 (1967: July 28)
  - Item 29: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.29 (1967: Aug. 4)
  - Item 30: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.30 (1967: Aug. 11)
  - Item 31: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.31 (1967: Aug. 18)
  - Item 32: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.32 (1967: Aug. 25)
  - Item 33: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.33 (1967: Sept. 1)
  - Item 34: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.34 (1967: Sept. 8)
  - Item 35: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.35 (1967: Sept. 15)
  - Item 36: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.36 (1967: Sept. 22)
  - Item 37: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.37 (1967: Sept. 29)
  - Item 38: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.38 (1967: Oct. 6)
  - Item 39: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.39 (1967: Oct. 13)
  - Item 40: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.40 (1967: Oct. 20)
  - Item 41: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.41 (1967: Oct. 27)
  - Item 42: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.42 (1967: Nov. 3)
  - Item 43: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.43 (1967: Nov. 10)
  - Item 44: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.44 (1967: Nov. 17)
  - Item 45: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.45 (1967: Dec. 1)
  - Item 46: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.46 (1967: Dec. 15)
  - Item 47: Locomotive Engineer, 1967; Publication (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.101:no.47 (1967: Dec. 22)
- Locomotive Engineer, 1968-1969 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.1 (1968: Jan. 5)
  - Item 2: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.2 (1968: Jan. 12)
  - Item 3: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.3 (1968: Jan. 29)
  - Item 4: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.4 (1968: Jan. 26)
  - Item 5: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.5 (1968: Feb. 2)
  - Item 6: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.6 (1968: Feb. 9)
  - Item 7: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.7 (1968: Feb. 16)
  - Item 8: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.8 (1968: Feb. 23)
  - Item 9: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.9 (1968: Mar. 1)
  - Item 10: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.10 (1968: Mar. 8)
  - Item 11: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.11 (1968: Mar. 15)
  - Item 12: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.12 (1968: Mar. 22)
  - Item 13: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.13 (1968: Mar. 29)
  - Item 14: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.14 (1968: Apr. 5)
  - Item 15: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.15 (1968: Apr. 12)
  - Item 16: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.102:no.16 (1968: Apr. 19)
  - Item 17: Locomotive Engineer, 1968; Publication (Box 48, Folder 2)